Curriculum Vita of

Md. Humayun Kabir Mobile : +8801791355666



Career Objective:

I would like to devote all my knowledge, skill and experience to any professional in a prosperous way where honestly, transparency and accountability would be evaluated. I will provide the best performance with the help of my previous experience and energy. I could utilize the opportunity to strengthen the organization and build up my own career also.

Education Information:

Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)

Group	:	Business Study	
Board		Dhaka	
Passing Year		2002	
Result	:	GPA-4.25	
Institute	:	Mymensingh Zilla School	

Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C)

Group	:	Business Study	
Board		Dhaka	
Passing Year	:	2004	
Result	:	GPA-3.36	
Institute	:	Mymensingh Govt. Commercial College	

Bachelor of Business Studies (B.B.S)

Subject	:	Management		
University	:	National University		
Passing Year	:	2008		
Result	:	2 nd Class		
Institute	:	Anandamohan College Mymensingh		

Masters of Business Studies (M.B.S)

Subject	:	Management		
University		National University		
Passing Year	:	2009		
Result	:	2 nd Class		
Institute	:	Anandamohan College Mymensingh		

Computer Skill:

Ms Word, Ms Excel, Microfin-360, Jobra Software, Swasti Software

Personal Information:

1	Name	:	Md. Humayun Kabir		
2	Father's Name	:	Sheikh Shajahan Kabir		
3	Mother's Name	:	Mst. Laily Begum		
4	Date of Birth	:	30 December, 1986		
5	Religion	:	Islam		
6	Gender	:	Male		
7	Marital Status	:	Married		
8	National ID No	:	283 157 2298		
9	Nationality	:	Bangladeshi		

Language Proficiency:

Bengali : Mother Tongue English : Workable

Experience:

* ASA- As a loan officer since	14-11-2011 to 04-02-2014
* SSS- Assistant Branch Manager Since	05-02-2014 to 24-11-2014
* SSS- Branch Manager Since	25-11-2014 to 18-01-2016
* SEBA- Branch Manager Since	13-04-2017 to 08-03-2018
* DSK- Branch Manager Since	11-05-2018 to 22-12-2018

Contact Information:

Present Address : Vill : batali Sheikh Bari, P.O: Attarampur (Betagair)

Upazilla: Nandail, Dist: Mymensingh

Permanent Address : Vill : batali Sheikh Bari, P.O: Attarampur (Betagair)

Upazilla: Nandail, Dist: Mymensingh

Mobile : +8801791-355666, +8801680-287044

Reference:

S.M. Hafijur Rahman	Abdul Mannan
Bangladesh Army	Business Man
Cumilla Cantonment	Sumi Basrobitan, Ganginarpar
Mobile: +8801750-491767	Mobile: +8801712-647900

Date : Md.Humayun Kabir